#### Jonathan Camilo Narvaez Martinez

Software Engineer, Frontend Developer, ReactJS.

(+57) 313 6482 103 (+57) 317 8559 796

Time zone: Bogotá, Colombia joncyy 19@hotmail.com jonxthxn1911@gmail.com https://github.com/Naramatsu https://curriculum-jcnm.vercel.app

Software Engineer with 3+ years of experience developing web applications using ReactJS, HTML5, CSS3 and SASS. Involved in building high scalable frontend components and backend APIs standardization to speed up programming. Very interested in working under organized software development methodologies, also in contributing to find clean and optime solutions to facilitate and expedite the maintainability and development of world-class software. In love with ReactJS on Frontend and NodeJS on Backend. In addition I've the ability to lead and perform teamwork; a person qualified to follow and receive orders of high responsibilities. I am ready to apply the knowledge learned and willing to continue with the intellectual formation. I adapt easily to different environments.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Freelance Frontend Developer UI/UX Designer (Cartagena, Colombia) — Oct 2021 - current — (Personal Projects)

- Kromac-UI (Style framework) is a 100% responsive style framework that seeks to facilitate the development and implementation of eye-catching components with modern styles to web applications.
  - Develop reusable and scalable components which are very easy to implement in an external react project.
  - Design of the components.
  - Maintain the framework.
  - Adding new Features.
  - o Fixing bugs.
- Mockups for a Store application.
  - Design a minimalistic web application with easy access to components
  - Create style components to reuse, creating variants, etc.

### EPAM, ReactJS Web UI Developer (Cartagena, Colombia) — May 2022 - Sep 2022

- Growth (Improving and acquiring knowledge) Reinforcing knowledge in ReactJS, React hooks, ReactJs + Typescript, React Native (for android) and NextJS. Learning basic concepts in user interface design with Figma, I worked on personal projects like: OAuth login services with JWT + Google + NodeJS, News application for android devices, Mockups for a Store application.
  - o Develop reusable and scalable applications.
  - Using github

#### Condor Labs, Full Stack Developer (Cartagena, Colombia) — May 2020 - May 2022

- Education web application Creation of an application in ReactJS + SASS + Redux + NojdeJS + Express + MongoDB + OracleDB + AWS stack, conformed by a group of 3 backend developers and 1 frontend developer, each one was in charge of features created in the backlog according to the Product Owner projections.
  - o Develop reusable and scalable components.
  - Maintaining components, applications and microservices in order for the user has a very good user experience.
  - Standardization, documentation and APIs simplification of the main core components, design systems improving the components reusability.
  - Implementing tools for forms to handle validations in frontend and backend through a JSON schema using React Hook Forms.
  - Planning and estimation tasks to work for a quarter (3 months).
  - Unit testing with Jest of the different frontend application elements like components, reducers, hooks and util functions.
  - o Using github
  - Play under SCRUM methodology.

#### Zeus tecnologias, Full Stack Developer (Cartagena, Colombia) — May 2019 - May 2020

- Restaurant Application Maintaining an application in Foxpro, Visual Basic and migrating to ASP .Net, conformed by a group of 3 full stack developers, each one was in charge of features created in the backlog according to the Product Owner projections.
  - o Adding new features.
  - Real-time customer support.
  - Standardization and documentation of the main core components, and user manual.
  - Using github
  - Play under SCRUM methodology.

#### VISO Infinity Travels, Practitioner (Cartagena, Colombia) — Dec 2018 - May 2019

- Web site and application Creation of the main website of the enterprise, maintaining the content, updating new offerts, conformed by a group of 2 full stack developers, each one was in charge of features created in the backlog.
  - Creation of the website and application.
  - Adding new features.
  - Keep up to date the information...
  - Standardization and documentation of the main core components, and user manual.
  - Using github
  - Play under SCRUM methodology.

### **EDUCATION**

# Systems Engineering (Cartagena, Colombia) — Jan 2014 - Apr 2020

• Fundacion Universitaria Tecnologico Comfenalco

# High school (Turbaco, Colombia) — Dec 2013

• Institucion Educativa Docente de Turbaco